# Jeremy (Mingxuan) Li

39 Florence St, Malden, MA, 02148

Email: jeremyli.9023@gmail.com

# **Objective**

A dedicated software engineer who has 3+ years industry experiences based on extensive practices in programming/engineering with Java, JavaScript. My passion and vision is to launch pixel-free software product with delightful user experience for others.

# **Work Experiences**

# Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA

## Software Engineer, Developer Integration

Mar, 2018 - Now

Tel: (781)-605-7163

- Built friction-less third-party plugins/toolings to support developer-friendly technical community.
- Scaled Jira standalone server over AWS cloud-based ecosystem to reduce massive single point failures.
- Built up customer metrics via SumoLogic to track real-time API calling through the entire integration eco-system(7 product lines), to help senior management and partners make strategic roadmap decisions.
- $\bullet$  Exposed proactively in Scrum and DevOps realm(A/B test, canary releases) to gain better product sense and SaaS enterprise insights.

# CA Technologies, Burlington, MA

### Software Engineer I, Developer Integration

Nov, 2017 - Mar, 2018

• Implement and maintain a range of plugins/extensions of SaaS application security scan platform, led to increased at least 20% efficiency of proceeding application security scanning assessment.

# Veracode, Inc, Burlington, MA (Acquired by CA Technologies March, 2017)

# Software Engineer I, Core Platform

Jun, 2016 – Nov,2017

- Collaborated with Designer, PM and QA to bring new features/enhancements onto team by using Agile.
- Tackled customer-faced technical problems, refactored the deprecated codebase and integrated with CI/CD pipeline, improved our SDLC for a more reliable TDD environment.
- Been UX council member dedicated to my team, to unify and adopt best practice of front-end effort needed along with product roadmap.

## Philips of North America, New York

#### Software Research Intern, Acute Care Solution

Sep – Dec, 2014

- Processed and transformed healthcare dataset that can be later used for EMR research purposes.
- Implemented a periodic recommendation for patient monitoring system by using Python.

# **Technical Skills**

- ► Languages: Java, Javascript/ES6, Python, R, HTML5/CSS3(Sass/LESS) 
  ► Databases: MySQL
- ▶ Web Framework: React, D3.js, Jest, Bootstrap, Foundation, Gulp, Bower, RESTful, Spring Boot.
- ▶ DevOps: AWS, Jenkins, Docker ▶ Other: Git/Bitbucket, Jira/Confluence, Agile, Axure, Balsamiq.
- ► Certification: PSM I (Professional Scrum Master), Google Analytics IQ.

#### Education

## Northeastern University, College of Engineering, Boston, MA

M.S. in Information Systems

Sep, 2015

Related Course: Java Application Engineering, Web Development/Design, Advanced Data Science, etc.

## Central South University, College of Engineering, Changsha, China

## Monash University, College of Engineering, Melbourne, Australia

B.S. in Computational Material Engineering

Jun, 2013

Honors: 2nd prize in Challenge Cup Innovative Technology; "Most Influential Member", Engineer-Club. Leadership: College Vice-President of Innovation and Entrepreneurship Association.

# **Academic Projects**

## **U.S. Airlines On-Time Performance Analytics Project**

- Cleaned, assembled and transformed the large-scale datasets from RITA.(K-Mean, Hclust, dbscan).
- Delivered graphs and charts for visualizing air flight on-time performance analysis outcomes.

#### **Healthcare Medical-Malpractice Informatics System**

- Designed a national-wide model independently for adverse reporting of the healthcare system by Java.
- Implemented a hierarchical access system to safeguard patient privacy under aggressive deadlines.